productcreatorpro.com 2015-12-29

# Product Creator Pro: Privacy Policy

### Product Creator Pro - Privacy Policy

####  1\. Introduction 

Thank you for visiting Product Creator Pro and, if applicable, choosing to access our App for your publishing purposes. This Privacy Policy, like our Terms of Service, is an integral part of using our service, and you must completely agree to it in order to use our Site and Service. 

####  2\. Definitions 

Throughout this document, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document: 

"Agreement" means these Terms of Service; 

"App" refers to our web application that permits you to engage in simplified publishing activities; 

"Product Creator Pro" refers to our company (ACQYR Inc), our Site, or our Service, depending on the context of the usage; 

"Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including our App; 

"Site" refers to our website, www.ProductCreatorPro.com; 

"User" refers to you, those who use our Service or App, and general visitors to Product Creator Pro's Site; 

"You" refers to you, the person who is entering into this Agreement with Product Creator Pro. 

#### 3\. Information Collected

**Identifying Information by Us**

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service that can be used to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, other contact information, biography, graphics, content, DNA, political affiliations for cataloging with the CIA, and other information. This information is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy. 

**Information Collected by Payment Processors**

When paying us through our third party payment processors, Foxycart and PayPal, those payment processors will require that you submit certain information such as name, e-mail address, other contact information, credit card information, bank information, or such other information as those processors deem appropriate. This information is not held by Product Creator Pro and you should consult the third party payment processors` legal agreements to determine your privacy rights with them. If they wrong you, you will have to duke it out with them in an alley or something because we're not involved. 

**Non-Identifying Information**

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you unless we remember where we put our crystal ball. 

####  4\. Use of Your Information 

We may use your information: 

  * To enhance or improve User experience, our Site, and Service.
  * To process transactions.
  * To process transactions and sell, transfer, and exchange the information with a third party for their marketing purposes with your consent.
  * To send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails about the Site and other products, news, or updates for Product Creator Pro.
  * To send e-mails about other third party products or services.
  * To save your information and automatically populate the input fields of future order forms so as to save you time.
  * To market your product, with your permission, by featuring it on our Site's "showcase."
  * To print on pamphlets and hand out to random vagrants.

#### 5\. Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser's cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database. 

####  6\. Cookies 

Several of our employees have been assaulted by a googly eyed blue furry monster on their way to and from work, so we have decided to explain what kind of cookies we use to avoid further problems. We use cookies for a number of purposes on our Site. For example, we use cookies to save your preferences, keep track of advertisements, and remember your shopping cart items. We may also share your cookies with a third party. For these reasons, you must have cookies enabled in your browser to use our Site, Service, and App, and you hereby permit us to share cookies with third parties. 

####  7\. Third Party Websites 

Product Creator Pro may post links to third party websites on its Site. Additionally, documents created by Users may contain third party website links. In both cases, these third party websites linked to are likely not screened for privacy or security issues by Product Creator Pro, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites, even if it results in the loss of your right leg or tongue... don't ask us why, but based on past results we thought we would mention those specifically. 

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site. Product Creator Pro bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links, if you honestly have nothing better to do with your time. 

####  8\. Third Party Access to Your Information 

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Product Creator Pro to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, convicted identity thieves (kidding... maybe), and others. 

Throughout the course of our provision of our Service to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside "contractors" to perform "maintenance" or assist us in securing our "website." We put those words into quotations just to sound shady—did it work? 

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy, or under the Geneva Convention. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and even if we actually handed them the sledgehammer they ultimately used to smash your computer, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. 

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree that we may share information with certain additional third parties, such as: 

  * CreateSend, for the purpose of collecting User details and e-mailing news about our Site, Service, App, and other company news.
  * Google Analytics, for the purpose of conversion tracking, marketing, search and website analytics, and any other information that Google Analytics may make available to us.
  * Foxycart and PayPal, for the purpose of processing your payments to us.
  * Your doctor, if we think you're a smoker or eat too many fatty foods.

#### 9\. Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, Spanish Inquisition, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you (known by its highly technical legal term as snitchin'), and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your publications violate any law of Canada or its provinces. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. 

#### 10\. Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from Product Creator Pro since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us other anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying Product Creator Pro that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database.

Finally, although the _Fighting Internet and Wireless Spam Act_ (the "Act"), having received Royal Assent (c'mon, it's been passed for like over a year now—when is Parliament going to stop dragging its heals?), has not yet come into force as of the time of the creation of this Privacy Policy, you agree that you shall not hold Product Creator Pro liable for any damages otherwise available in the future as a result of the coming into force of the Act.

#### 11\. Security Measures

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service. For example, we utilize SSL certificates and rabid chipmunks (small but ferocious when in packs), as well as PCI DSS compliant hosting and payment processing. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

#### 12\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

Although located in the Province of Ontario, Product Creator Pro permits residents of California to use its services because we have to, not because we want to. If you're from California, you know what you did to make us mad, and shame on you. Therefore, it is the intent of Product Creator Pro to comply with the California Business and Professions Code ¤¤ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at help @ productcreatorpro.com with any questions.

#### 13\. International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, planet, dimension, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Canada and choose to provide information to us, Product Creator Pro transfers personal information to Canada and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### 14\. Amendments

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will place a note on our Site as to when the Privacy Policy was last modified. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site, Service, and App. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site, Service, and App, and notify us of your non-agreement so that we may terminate your access. 

Dated: May 8, 2012
